[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the missing number in the following sequence:  4, 20, 24, ___, 44, 60, 64?", "correct_answer": "40", "incorrect_answers": ["28", "30", "32"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Pandas spend 10-16 hours a day eating, the rest of the time they are usually resting. When are pandas most active?", "correct_answer": "at dusk and at dawn", "incorrect_answers": ["between 10am and 2pm", "between 2p and 10pm", "only at night"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Rocky IV, Dragos wife was said to be a double gold medalist at the Olympics in which sport?", "correct_answer": "Swimming", "incorrect_answers": ["Archery", "Athletics", "Diving"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The 1962 Soccer World Cup tournament was held in this country.", "correct_answer": "Chile", "incorrect_answers": ["Switzerland", "Mexico", "Italy"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What 1970 movie was honored with an Academy Award for Best Picture at the 43rd Academy Awards in 1971?", "correct_answer": "Patton", "incorrect_answers": ["Five Easy Pieces", "Love Story", "Airport"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "All of these gadgets belong to James Bond except one.  Can you spot it?", "correct_answer": "Batarang", "incorrect_answers": ["Cigarette lighter (a disguised timed explosive)", "Polarizing Sunglasses", "Phone Booth Trap"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "While in the military, Johnny Cash is inspired by a film about a prison and its inmates and composes what famous song?", "correct_answer": "Folsom Prison Blues", "incorrect_answers": ["Behind These Folsom Walls", "Ring of Fire", "Folsom Blues"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which animal is NOT heard amongst the jungle noises in the opening Indiana Jones daydream sequence from the movie UHF?", "correct_answer": "Horse", "incorrect_answers": ["Cat", "Cow", "Dog"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "You have a string that is 120 inches. You must use this to enclose a shape of maximum area. What shape should  you form?", "correct_answer": "A circle of circumference 120 inches", "incorrect_answers": ["A square of 60 inches on each side", "A square of 30 inches on each side", "A triangle of 30 inches on each side"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Sylvester Stallone doesnt like his first name (this is true). When he was a kid, he decided to name himself Mike.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Ghost, Molly and Carl were going through a box of Sams things.  What goofy item did Molly want to keep that belonged to Sam?", "correct_answer": "Rolaids", "incorrect_answers": ["Gum", "Mints", "Toothpaste"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What state was the setting of the film The Blair Witch Project?", "correct_answer": "Maryland", "incorrect_answers": ["Vermont", "New Jersey", "Massachusetts"]}]